Question 1-3
Attention, Food Market shoppers.
2 This is your Food Market manager, Lisa Stanley,
1 alerting you to some fantastic deals we have for you this afternoon.
In our fruit section,
delicious red apples are just a dollar a kilogram!
Also, customers with a Food Market shopper's card
can purchase Oat Crunch breakfast cereal at half price.
Don't miss out on the savings in our drinks aisle,
where we are offering all customers a discount
on six-packs of Springvale Mineral Water.
And 3 remember to pick up your complimentary shopping bag before you leave.
It's our way of thanking you for shopping with us!
Question 4-6
Attention, passengers.
4,5 Because of track work north of Boston,
all arriving trains that pass through that region
are operating at slower speeds
and experiencing delays of approximately 45 minutes.
At present, the Montreal trains are not affected.
Please check the status of your train on the arrivals board,
which is updated every ten minutes.
Also, please be advised that due to engine trouble,
departing Train 55 to Vermont is not yet ready to receive passengers.
6 Wait for the boarding announcement before proceeding to the track.
Question 7-9
7 Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for joining us
at tonight's performance of Geraldine Ephart's new play,
"The Lion's Tale.”
7,8 Due to a minor difficulty with the sound system,
we ask that you remain here in the lobby
until we've fixed the problem.
9 Please visit the snack bar, which has coffee, tea,
soft drinks, and light snacks available for purchase.
We expect that you'll be able to take your seats in the theater in about fifteen minutes.
Again, we apologize for the delay.
Question 10-12
10 Attention Hamilton Grocery Shoppers!
Thank you for shopping with us today.
11 We would appreciate it if you would ﬁll out our customer survey.
We have two tables set up for your convenience
staffed by our customer service representatives
- one in the fruit section and one in front of the bakery.
It'll only take a minute, and will help us find out
how we can better serve our customers to the best of our abilities.
12 Those who complete the survey will receive a voucher
for 5 percent off all your purchases today.
Thank you, and have a great day!
Question 13-15
13 The city of Dover would like to inform residents of the following upcoming construction work.
14 Beginning Monday, August 8,
Main Street will be closed for water pipe installation.
Automobile traffic will not be allowed on Main Street between Sixteenth Street and Twentieth Street.
Pedestrians will be able to access all stores in the area
while the work is being completed.
We expect to reopen Main Street by August 11.
We apologize for any inconvenience this closure may cause.
15 If you have any questions regarding the construction on Main Street,
please call the City Planning Office at 555-3701.
Question 16-18
Attention shoppers: 16 Our store will be closing in fifteen minutes.
Please make your final selections and proceed to the checkout line.
Don't forget today's specials in the fruits and vegetables section:
all Florida oranges and grapefruit, just two dollars a kilo
- but only for a few more minutes!
17 The customer service counter is now closed;
please direct all questions to the manager on duty.
18 We're proud to announce that we've extended our hours of operation in order to serve you better.
Starting next week, our new hours will be from seven A.M. to nine P.M., seven days a week.
Thank you for shopping with us, and we look forward to seeing you again.
Question 19-21
Attention, passengers.
Welcome aboard Trilsen Airways flight 209 with nonstop service to Seattle.
19 At this time, please make sure your bags and personal items are properly stowed
in the overhead bins or under the seat ahead of you.
20 Our flight today will be about six hours long,
and we expect an on-time arrival.
We'll be taking off in just a few minutes,
so I'd like to remind you that wireless Internet access is available on this flight.
You can refer to the brochure in your seat-back pocket for pricing options.
21 Once our cruising altitude has been reached,
flight attendants will come around with our complimentary beverage service.